(Penny:)I wish I felt more confident.
Penny,
(Bernadette:)I wouldn't have put
you up for this job
(Bernadette:)if I didn't think
you could handle it.
(Penny:)Oh, thank you,
but maybe I should cancel.
(Bernadette:)It's too late to cancel.
You're going.
(Penny:)But I don't know anything
about pharmaceuticals.
(Bernadette:)Oh, I understand.
(Bernadette:)You want to do something
you're already good at.
(Sheldon:)I know.
(Bernadette:)Why don't I get
you a job at
(Bernadette:)the Sitting Around All Day
Wearing Yoga Pants Factory?
(Penny:)They're comfortable.
(Howard:)Ma, I hope you're decent.
Raj is here!
(Howard:)You just started seeing
naked women again,
(Howard:)and I don't want you
to be confused
(Howard:)about where the boobs should be.
(Stuart:)Oh, hey, guys.
(Howard:)What are you
doing here?
Uh... w-what are you doing here?
(Howard:)I thought you moved out.
(Stuart:)Oh, yeah, I was going to,
(Stuart:)and then Debbie
and I got to talking
(Stuart:)over dinner
the other night.
I didn't have anyplace to go,
(Stuart:)she likes having me around,
so we both said, "Why leave?"
at the same time.
(laughs)
(Stuart:)It was precious.